{
    "id": "798bc5a086a046bcbfd709a844acde6c",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There ………………………….. a famine in Bengal in",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished actions and situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Gandhi …………………………… in the principle of non-violence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "believed",
                "has believed",
                "believes"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They have not …………………………. yet.",
            "description": "We use a past participle form after has, have and had.",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "arriving",
                "arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… not want to quit her job.",
            "description": "We make questions and negatives in the simple present tense with do and does. We use does with singular nouns and pronouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The ozone layer ……………………………… us from harmful ultraviolet radiations.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "protect",
                "protects",
                "is protecting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………… her studies before she went abroad.",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of two past actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "completed",
                "has completed",
                "had completed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. him on several occasions before he went to America.",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of two past actions or situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Jenny …………………………….. alone in her apartment.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "is living"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was young, I …………………………… every day.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about past habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "worked out",
                "was working out",
                "had worked out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………………. for Malaysia tonight.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about pre-planned future events. ",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "will leave",
                "are leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Barking dogs seldom …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bite",
                "will bite",
                "would bite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you ………………………………. him yesterday?",
            "description": "We use the first form of the verb after do, does and did.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "saw",
                "seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}